themefisher.com 2018-10-14

# Privacy Policy - Themefisher

We ThemeFisher commit ourselves to protecting and respecting your privacy when visiting our website.

This privacy policy discloses how we will treat and use any personal data that you provide deliberately to us, or that we may collect as a result of visiting our site.

Please before accessing the website read this privacy policy to understand our practices with regards to your personal information and how we will treat it.

#### What information is collected by ThemeFisher.com?

#### Standard use of the Site:

In general, you can browse this site without telling us who you are or revealing any of your personal information. The only information we gather while browsing the site is the information intended for the server logs. Such as the type of browser, operating system, IP (Internet Protocol) address, domain name, and information such as the site of which you are connected, pages visited, and the dates and times of those visits.

#### Collect of Personal Information:

If you subscribe to a newsletter, contact us, request information, send any comments you will need to provide some personal information: e-mail address and name, for example. Such information is collected only with your permission and stored in different databases and mailing lists belonging to ThemeFisher.com.

#### What does ThemeFisher.com do with the information we collect?

#### Standard use of the Site:

The information we collect during the navigation in the ThemeFisher.com area is used to analyze trends and the use of the site to improve its usefulness. No personal information is attached there.

ThemeFisher.com may use such information to:

Contact with you – either in response to a request or a suggestion, or to send you news, documents, publications, and so on;

Confirm your entries on the site;

Statistical analysis performing

#### What will happen if I don't want to provide any personal information?

Providing your personal information on the site is optional. If you don’t want to deliver information of this kind, you can always visit the site, but you won’t able to access the entire service, newsletters, and other informative information.

#### Removal or Modification of Information:

You can unsubscribe from our email subscription at any time by returning to the page or by contacting the coordinator of the page.

The personal data that consigned to the site will not be sold or transferred to any third party. Any information provided to ThemeFisher.com by users of the site preserved with the highest care and maximum safety. It will be used only for the use described in this privacy policy, or according to the particular rules of visited sites or in a manner to which you have explicitly consented. ThemeFisher.com uses techniques and a variety of measures to assure the safety of information collected in its systems and protects them from damage, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or destruction.

All our volunteers who have access to personal information or associated with the processing of these data are bound to respect the confidentiality of every user of the site, which comprises the personal information.

The site presents links to outside the ThemeFisher.com could not be held responsible for the privacy policies or the content located on them.

Any change of these terms can make at any time without prior publication or announcement.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

themefisher.com

Dhaka,

Bangladesh

Or you can also email us to themefisher@gmail.com
